{
    "id": "c475663924994e9c9e813e4b0520a336",
    "title": "Gerunds or Infinitives",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I still remember …………………… my first bike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "buying",
                "to buy"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "55351e177b464510b87b95c28fb4d48d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must remember …………………. him from the station tomorrow.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fetching",
                "to fetch"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "85c2f08d528545958a8c38fd17a20226"
        },
        {
            "question": "I regret ……………………… school at 13 – it was a big mistake.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leaving",
                "to leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5930b6d320834763867db05420a89c50"
        },
        {
            "question": "We don’t allow people …………………… in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoking",
                "to smoke"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b0c0f20eb36412fa0efbb845cd1921e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I slowly began ……………………… what she meant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to understand",
                "understanding"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "157f9d0487db43e9b0630413214fd984"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget ………………… the Queen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to meet",
                "meeting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81d0426bb28441ed93c7145eb59c17b7"
        },
        {
            "question": "We regret ………………… that we are unable to help you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to say",
                "saying"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6f477e591f1a42998e7866d14afe5ed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am interested in ……………………  in France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "working",
                "to work"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "50ad0b866bfa4f2595d080a756dd4921"
        },
        {
            "question": "We look forward to ………………… from you soon.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e2e3930af82447eabc302f070096c48"
        },
        {
            "question": "People are not allowed …………………… in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to smoke",
                "smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f5f9a228c2564e0b9d0a5b5cdfe5e83d"
        }
    ]
}